I hope you will
accept my heart, my lord.
Lady Elowen, you must be mistaken.
Severin is just a disowned son.
Redmond is the true
heir of House Carter.
You dare question my judgment?
Offending Lord Severin means declaring
war on the entire Morellan family.
He’s nothing but a miner
who digs in the dirt!
I am the rightful heir. Why choose this failure?
Who the hell do
you think you are?
You’re not even worthy of breathing
the same air as Lord Severin.
That’s why I
publicly ended the engagement.
He must have used
some sorcery to trick you.
He didn’t trick me.
You're the one who couldn't recognize a true
god standing right in front of you.
Impossible.
A failure who spends
his time with lowborn miners,
how could he
possibly
be a true god?
I see now.
It’s not that you don’t believe it .
You just can't stand it.
Lord Severin, please accept my proposal.
I swear on the Morellan
family name that I will
be loyal to you for
the rest of my life.
We beg you
to accept, Lord Severin!
Mother, what do you think?
Yes!
She’s perfect!
Thank you, Mother.
And what is
your answer, my lord?
Very well.
Across all of Golantis,
there truly is no
woman more outstanding than you.
Today, I accept your proposal.